model company. So basically you just set up, okay I need a robotic campaign and I
模范公司。所以基本上你只需设置，好吧，我需要一个机器人活动，我
need a maybe person from the Philippines to annotate this side of the data and
需要一个来自菲律宾的人来注释数据的这一面并且
the task will render automatically. You can see the revenue stream all the way.
任务将自动渲染。您可以一路看到收入来源。
That's our takeaway. So we just leverage the blockchain to track our
这就是我们的收获。所以我们只是利用区块链来追踪我们的
DID or 402 protocol to track our revenue and also data lineage.
DID 或 402 协议来跟踪我们的收入和数据沿袭。
Thanks. Thank you Kevin for the inspiring speech. And next we will welcome Primus.
谢谢。感谢凯文的鼓舞人心的演讲。接下来我们将迎来 Primus。
Hello everyone. I'm Xavier from Primus. I'm the developer and the co-founder of the
大家好。我是来自 Primus 的泽维尔。我是开发者和联合创始人
team. So today I would like to show you something that solves a fundamental
团队。所以今天我想向你们展示一些可以解决根本问题的东西
blockchain problem. So that is how can we keep the financial transaction private
区块链问题。这就是我们如何保持金融交易的私密性
while still making it auditable. Primus is building a verification and the
同时仍使其可审计。 Primus 正在构建验证和
privacy layer with two core technologies. One is CKTS, the Zero Knowledge Transport
隐私层有两大核心技术。一是CKTS，零知识传输
Layer Security. It's a very cool technology that lets you to prove any off-chain
层安全。这是一项非常酷的技术，可以让你证明任何链下
data. Something like your account ownership, your API execution, your
数据。比如您的帐户所有权、您的 API 执行、您的
bank balance. And the power is it allows you to prove the data is correct without
银行余额。它的强大之处在于它可以让你证明数据是正确的，而无需
even revealing the underlying content. And the second technology, FHE,
甚至揭示底层内容。第二种技术，FHE，
fully homomorphic encryption, which is the star of the demo. It allows you to
完全同态加密，这是演示的亮点。它可以让你
perform arbitrary computation on the encrypted data. So basically the data
对加密数据进行任意计算。所以基本上数据
doesn't need to be decrypted and to be processed. And the Primus is even
不需要解密和处理。 Primus 甚至
building a new protocol called ZKFHE or Verifiable FHE. It provides the
构建一个名为 ZKFHE 或可验证 FHE 的新协议。它提供了
further computation integrity to the homomorphic encryption. So which means
同态加密的进一步计算完整性。那么这意味着
the data is during the data processing you not only get the result from the
数据在数据处理过程中你不仅得到结果
encrypted computation process, you also get a proof which states the data is
加密计算过程中，您还可以获得一个证明，表明数据是
correctly computed. So Primus is offering this kind of cryptographic
正确计算。所以 Primus 提供了这种加密技术
native verifiability and the privacy for multiple blockchains and for different
多个区块链和不同区块链的本机可验证性和隐私性
applications including AI agents. On the technical side, the FHE
包括人工智能代理在内的应用程序。在技​​术方面，FHE
computing infrastructure we built here. We just built some system contract
我们在这里建造的计算基础设施。我们刚刚构建了一些系统合约
on the host blockchain and the core component we call the alpha chain is a
在主机区块链上，我们称之为阿尔法链的核心组件是
real FHE engine doing the FHE operations of chain. And also we use the TE
真正的FHE引擎执行链的FHE操作。我们也使用 TE
technologies to handle the key measurement to further secure the whole
技术来处理关键测量，以进一步确保整体安全
system. So here's a demo we built called Auditable Private Transfer. It's very
系统。这是我们构建的一个演示，名为“可审计的私人传输”。这是非常
simple. It allows you to transfer any plan money into the encrypted money we
简单的。它允许您将任何计划资金转入我们的加密资金
call the encrypted USDC here. And you can just transfer this encrypted money
这里调用加密的USDC。你可以直接转移这笔加密货币
between different wallet adjusts which means no one can see the details of the
不同钱包之间的调整意味着没有人可以看到钱包的详细信息
transfer transaction. And you can further withdraw this money back, convert the
转让交易。您可以进一步提取这笔钱，兑换
money from the encrypted version to the plain version. And also we support
钱从加密版本到明文版本。而且我们也支持
audit which means the audit is able to review and to see the details of
审核，这意味着审核能够审查并查看以下内容的详细信息
the transaction and of the account details. And we just use a very
交易和帐户详细信息。我们只是使用一个非常
lightweight architecture here. We build it on the EVM chain. Here we use the
这里是轻量级架构。我们将其构建在 EVM 链上。这里我们使用
Firest testnet and then we use just a full core cloud instance to
首先测试网，然后我们只使用一个完整的核心云实例
do such a demo. So here is the demo. So basically you just connect your wallet.
做一个这样的demo。这是演示。所以基本上你只需连接你的钱包即可。
Your first login with user we call Alice and you can decrypt to view how
您第一次登录我们称为 Alice 的用户，您可以解密以查看如何
much money Alice already has here. So he has some EUSDC which is the
爱丽丝已经有很多钱了。所以他有一些 EUSDC 这是
encrypted money and some USDC here. So first let's make Alice deposit
这里有加密货币和一些 USDC。首先让我们给爱丽丝存款
some USDC into her own account. So you just confirm the
一些 USDC 存入她自己的账户。所以你只需确认
transaction and wait a few seconds here after the transaction has been
交易并在交易完成后在此等待几秒钟
broadcasted and confirmed on the blockchain. So you just review and
在区块链上广播并确认。所以你只需回顾并
decrypt your balance. Wait a few seconds. So here is the FHC result. You got
解密您的余额。等几秒钟。这是 FHC 结果。你得到了
your balance here and you can further transfer your encrypted money which
您的余额在这里，您可以进一步转移您的加密货币
means you can transfer your EUSDC to another account or to your
意味着您可以将您的 EUSDC 转移到另一个账户或您的
friends. So let's copy the address from Bob and you'll copy the address here and
朋友们。因此，让我们复制 Bob 的地址，您将在此处复制该地址，然后
you specify how much money you want to transfer and they'll confirm the
您指定要转账的金额，他们会确认
transaction. So again the transaction is being broadcasted and being confirmed
交易。所以交易再次被广播并被确认
and they'll just further wait for a few seconds to make sure the transaction is
他们只会再等待几秒钟以确保交易完成
finalized. Okay you have the new money here and Alice is not able to be the
最终确定。好吧，你这里有新钱，爱丽丝不能成为
auditor. He cannot see anyone else's balance or account details. So let's
审计员。他无法看到其他人的余额或帐户详细信息。那么让我们
switch to another account. Let's use Bob's account here. So since Bob is
切换到另一个帐户。我们在这里使用 Bob 的帐户。所以既然鲍勃是
auditor already so he is able to access the audit portal and he is able to first
审计员已经这样他就能够访问审计门户并且他能够首先
can add other auditor to this portal which makes them be able to access the
可以将其他审核员添加到此门户，这使他们能够访问
details of the system and also he can first synchronize all the
系统的详细信息，他也可以首先同步所有
system users in this panel and he can further decrypt the balance of the
系统用户在这个面板中他可以进一步解密余额
other users here like this. So here's a demo and this is a very simple app we
这里的其他用户也这样。这是一个演示，这是一个非常简单的应用程序
build with FHE and we think this is not just a starting point of the
与 FHE 一起构建，我们认为这不仅仅是一个起点
technology but also it's very useful for the like institutions and the
技术，而且对于类似的机构和
compliant crypto financial here. So yeah thanks for watching. Thank you Primus
这里是合规的加密货币金融。所以是的，感谢您的观看。谢谢普里姆斯
for the live demo and next up please welcome Ninja. Hello so let's start. Okay
对于现场演示和接下来的内容，欢迎 Ninja。你好，让我们开始吧。好的
four years ago most of the on-chain theft was called hack but two years later
四年前，大多数链上盗窃被称为黑客攻击，但两年后
much of it has shifted to interface fraud. Attacast moved but defenders
其中大部分已转向界面欺诈。阿塔卡斯特移动但防守者
didn't. So what you see is what you sign is an essential idea to protect your
没有。因此，所见即所签是保护您的基本理念
assets but it is not enough. See and understand. You need to understand with
资产，但这还不够。看到并理解。你需要理解
complex transactions. So what you read is what you sign. It's a new idea simple
复杂的交易。所以你读到的就是你签名的。这是一个新的想法，简单
idea. Why is it read? This is a real attack contract you may remember it. There are a
主意。为什么会被读到？这是一个真实的攻击合约你可能还记得吧。有一个
lot of hex characters. Can you read it? But we can do that. Let me ask Ninja.
很多十六进制字符。你能读懂吗？但我们可以做到。我来问问忍者吧
Let's start. So it is a ninja scan demo screen so on Trillium bot. So initialize
让我们开始吧。这是 Trillium 机器人上的忍者扫描演示屏幕。所以初始化
the ninja scan and paste the suspicious contract code and then ninja scan
忍者扫描并粘贴可疑合同代码，然后忍者扫描
analyze and oh it's danger malicious proxy and war trainers and if you want
分析一下，哦，这是危险的恶意代理和战争训练员，如果你愿意的话
to see the details you can see it by natural language by LLM. If only ninja
要查看详细信息，您可以通过LLM的自然语言查看它。如果只是忍者的话
scan had been there before signing. 2.4 billion jealous last year was theft.
签字之前扫描已经在那里了。去年有24亿人嫉妒被盗窃。
Fishing, honey pots, others poisoning, most of them was catchable. So ninja is
钓鱼、蜜罐、其他投毒，大部分都是可以钓到的。所以忍者是
trust and risk intelligence layer between intent and execution. Three
意图和执行之间的信任和风险情报层。三
inputs. Entity is a smart contract and action transaction and position your
输入。实体是一个智能合约和行动交易，并定位您的
financial portfolio. Ninja, AI engine, analyze and visualize and two outputs.
金融投资组合。 Ninja，AI 引擎，分析和可视化以及两个输出。
One is a deterministic verdict safe or not by machine learning. We don't use
一是通过机器学习做出安全与否的确定性判断。我们不使用
LLM at that time. So we only use LLM natural language explanation of the
那时的LLM。所以我们只用LLM自然语言解释
transaction or code. Three diverse channels. Ninja scan, Trillium bot, API and
交易或代码。三个不同的渠道。 Ninja 扫描、Trillium 机器人、API 和
MCP. Why should you trust us? We already analyze over 90 millions of contracts.
MCP。您为什么应该信任我们？我们已经分析了超过 9000 万份合同。
Every contract on AVM. We classify nine vulnerabilities and we
AVM 上的每份合约。我们对九个漏洞进行了分类
score the similarity of existing vulnerable or malicious contract types.
对现有易受攻击或恶意合约类型的相似性进行评分。
Ninja is built for human today and ready for agents tomorrow. So we decided to
Ninja 是为今天的人类而打造，并为明天的特工做好准备。所以我们决定
adopt ELC 8004. It's a new standard of agents identity. This is our team. My name
采用ELC 8004。这是一个新的代理身份标准。这是我们的团队。我的名字
is Kazuki Kaneshiro, ZKAC founder and the ninja founders. So for many years I worked
是ZKAC创始人兼忍者创始人Kazuki Kaneshiro。所以我工作了很多年
on financial and AI a lot of projects in Japan and with me is Kai Otsuki, chief
在日本有很多关于金融和人工智能的项目，和我一起的是 Kai Otsuki，首席
scientist. He's an Ethereum committer. Two asks. We are looking for POC partners.
科学家。他是以太坊的提交者。二问。我们正在寻找 POC 合作伙伴。
World developers and DeFi protocols and AI agent developers. Talk to me later.
全球开发者以及 DeFi 协议和 AI 代理开发者。稍后再跟我说。
And investors. We are raising. Just talk to me later too. Two QRs. Left one is a
还有投资者。我们正在筹集资金。也晚点再跟我说吧。两个 QR。左边一个是一个
ninja scan. Try. You can try it from now on any contract and right one is my
忍者扫描。尝试。从现在开始你可以在任何合同上尝试，正确的一个是我的
cherry-gum QR. So give me feedback and talk to me later. Ninja is human today
樱桃胶 QR。所以请给我反馈并稍后再与我交谈。今天的忍者也是人类
and agents tomorrow. Thank you. Thank you, Ninja, for the live demo. Next up, please
明天还有代理商。谢谢。谢谢 Ninja 的现场演示。接下来请
welcome Sysic AI. Hello everyone. This is Leo from Sysic. So today I'm going to
欢迎 Sysic AI。大家好。我是 Sysic 的 Leo。所以今天我要
give you a preview of the things that we are building on our AI side. So AI
让您预览我们正在人工智能方面构建的东西。所以人工智能
products like previously like we used to deliver four thousand four hundred
像以前一样的产品，我们过去交付了四千四百件
thousands of lines of code and we thought like without any human in the loop for
数千行代码，我们认为循环中没有任何人
this like amount of coding project and the performance like we of this like
这就像编码项目的数量和像我们这样的性能
deliver code is like at least like 10 to 15 percent faster than the state of
交付代码的速度至少比状态快 10% 到 15%
art in the ZK proving site. Yeah we think like this this product may be also like
ZK 证明站点中的艺术。是的，我们认为这个产品可能也是这样
beneficial to the Ethereum or like a border community and like the whole
有利于以太坊或像边界社区一样整体
blockchain community. So I'm here to give you a like preview of the demo like we
区块链社区。所以我在这里给你一个像我们一样的演示预览
use we use this like AI product to build a flappy bird this kind of like a games
使用我们使用这个像人工智能产品一样构建一个像游戏一样的飞扬的小鸟
without any human in the loop thing. Okay so now let's take a look at the demo.
没有任何人参与循环。好的，现在让我们看一下演示。
Okay yeah so this AI product allows you to download the code like after like
好的，是的，所以这个人工智能产品允许您像之后一样下载代码
it's finished the job but you can also like integrate this AI product with
它完成了工作，但您也可以将此人工智能产品与
with your github. So like it will allow the agent to push code to your github
与你的github。就像它允许代理将代码推送到你的 github 上一样
repository and also like be author of this thing. So right now it's like doing
存储库，也喜欢成为这个东西的作者。所以现在就像做
this like API integration. So integrate the API in the in this tool and then
这就像 API 集成。所以将API集成到这个工具中然后
then analysis to push code like to the to the to the github repository. So right
然后分析将代码推送到 github 存储库。太对了
now like all the themes are set and you have this like API key then you can put
现在所有主题都已设置并且您拥有类似 API 密钥，然后您可以将
it in there and then you can choose your like AI models like you can plug in
它在那里，然后你可以选择你喜欢的人工智能模型，就像你可以插入一样
basically every open source model plus the closed source model and then after
基本上每个开源模型加上闭源模型，然后
that you start the process. So here is like you input the description of this
你开始这个过程。所以这里就像你输入这个的描述
game the flappy bird. There will be just a one round of interaction between you
游戏《飞扬的小鸟》。你们之间只会有一轮互动
and and the AI and now it starts working. So it will automatically generate all
还有人工智能，现在它开始工作了。所以它会自动生成所有
the codes in several hours. Without any human in the loop you do not need to
几个小时内的代码。没有任何人在循环中，您不需要
check the status of the theme. There will be like a bunch of like AI agents doing
检查主题的状态。将会有一群类似的人工智能代理在做
the coding while another bunch of like AI agents doing the like a review review.
编码，而另一群类似的人工智能代理则进行类似审查的审查。
It's basically the rough loop with code review if you are familiar with that.
如果您熟悉的话，这基本上是代码审查的粗略循环。
Yeah so like here is like generating all the code and like for each round it will
是的，就像这里生成所有代码一样，就像每一轮一样
provide you with a summary of like what they are doing what kind of like feature
为您提供一个总结，比如他们正在做什么，是什么样的功能
they add to your product. Yeah so right now still like working on the code and
他们添加到您的产品中。是的，所以现在仍然喜欢编写代码并且
you can set the maximum rounds complexity to be like five or ten it all
您可以将最大回合复杂度设置为五或十
depends on you. So after all after the code are you generated it will push the
取决于你。所以毕竟在你生成代码之后它会推送
codes to GitHub repository and you can check the commit you can check the
代码到 GitHub 存储库，您可以检查提交，您可以检查
Remy to find out like what they are actually doing and the contributors
雷米了解他们实际上在做什么以及贡献者
realize cloud. So you push like the agent will push all the things like to the to
实现云。所以你像代理一样推送所有的东西到
the github and like without any human interaction. Yeah so that's the code
github 等，无需任何人际交互。是的，这就是代码
like we're just going through all the files you changed and like all the
就像我们刚刚浏览您更改的所有文件一样
commits it made to this GitHub repository. Okay so now let's take a look at
将其提交到此 GitHub 存储库。好的，现在让我们看一下
the same. Like we asked them to to do like 70 or 80 something this flappy
相同。就像我们要求他们做 70 或 80 件这样的事情
So it's deliver the game in about like two hours and we have already show
所以它在大约两个小时内交付了游戏，我们已经展示了
that this idea can be used to also do like a very complicated project. So
这个想法也可以用来做一个非常复杂的项目。所以
basically you don't need a very large team or like several several months to
基本上你不需要一个非常大的团队或几个月的时间
do the product development. You just need one or two people and you can do
做产品开发。你只需要一两个人就可以做到
iteration like in weeks or probably like in days instead of in months. We are
迭代就像以周为单位，或者可能以天为单位，而不是以月为单位。我们是
about to launch this like product. If you are interested please stay tuned to
即将推出类似产品。如果您有兴趣请继续关注
our Twitter account. You can search it online. Okay bye. Thank you
我们的推特帐户。你可以去网上搜索一下。好的再见。谢谢
Sysic AI. Thank you for bringing us a useful tool for the builders and next up
系统人工智能。感谢您为我们带来了对构建者和下一步有用的工具
please welcome Privacy Pools. Thank you everyone. I'm really honored to be here.
欢迎隐私池。谢谢大家。我真的很荣幸来到这里。
I've been told that I'm given four minutes so I'll try and make this
有人告诉我有四分钟的时间，所以我会尽力做到这一点
relevant to you, interesting and entertaining. So I am Vailin. I am the
与您相关、有趣且有趣。所以我是维林。我是
APAC relations at Oxbow. At Oxbow we build privacy tooling such as privacy
Oxbow 的亚太地区关系。在 Oxbow，我们构建隐私工具，例如隐私
pools and compliant toolings for enterprises.
为企业提供池和合规工具。
We are a company that develops and uses online transaction privacy tools.
我们是一家开发和使用在线交易隐私工具的公司。
Products including privacy pools are tools for business and customers. So in this
包括隐私池在内的产品是企业和客户的工具。所以在这个
demo I will be talking about what your crypto card tells the world with the
演示 我将谈论您的加密卡通过以下方式告诉世界什么
increasing adoption of stable coins and stable coin payments. We need to think
越来越多地采用稳定币和稳定币支付。我们需要思考
seriously about improving the design choices of these products because every
认真地改进这些产品的设计选择，因为每一个
transaction is permanent and transparent on chain. And in this demo I'll be using
交易在链上永久透明。在这个演示中我将使用
Gnosis Pay card as an example but my analysis in this presentation applies
以 Gnosis Pay 卡为例，但我在本演示中的分析适用
for all self-custody card. So for Gnosis Card it has a lot of users. It has
适用于所有自助保管卡。所以对于Gnosis Card来说它有很多用户。它有
31,000 weekly card payments, 3,500 active card holders, 2 million weekly volume
每周卡付款 31,000 笔，活跃持卡人 3,500 名，周交易量 200 万笔
and most significantly 420% year-on-year growth. So every one of these
最显着的是同比增长420%。所以这些中的每一项
transactions is permanently stored on chain and there's no way of you deleting
交易永久存储在链上，您无法删除
that information or preventing other people from looking at your information.
该信息或阻止其他人查看您的信息。
So how Gnosis Pay actually works is that when you pull out your card to
因此，Gnosis Pay 的实际运作方式是，当您拿出卡来
pay for a coffee for example, Visa sends the auth request to Gnosis Pay, stable
例如，支付一杯咖啡的费用，Visa 将身份验证请求发送到 Gnosis Pay，稳定
coin transfer executes on chain from your wallet to the Gnosis Pay settlement
代币从您的钱包到 Gnosis Pay 结算的链上转账
safe and then after that to Visa. So what's public is actually how much you
安全，然后再去签证。所以公开的实际上是你有多少
spend, the exact time spent when you spend that amount of money, your current
花费，当你花费这笔钱时花费的确切时间，你当前的
balance and your entire transaction history. We don't know the merchant name,
余额和您的整个交易历史记录。我们不知道商家名称，
we don't know what you exactly buy and we don't know where you exactly buy the
我们不知道您到底买了什么，也不知道您到底在哪里买的
thing from but we don't need to know to identify your entire financial footprint
但我们不需要知道即可确定您的整个财务足迹
because the amount and the timing is enough and what I mean by that, so my
因为数量和时间都足够了，我的意思是，所以我的
team and I actually found every card holder on the Gnosis Pay card and all we
我和团队实际上找到了 Gnosis Pay 卡上的每个持卡人以及我们所有人
need to do is to find a single settlement vault to identify their
需要做的是找到一个单一的结算金库来识别他们的
spending patterns. So take this pseudonymous person for example, we
支出模式。那么以这个化名的人为例，我们
found eight different points where he spent their money and we could
找到了他花钱的八个不同的地方，我们可以
make educated guesses what exactly they spent on when and how. So we could guess
做出有根据的猜测，他们究竟在何时以及如何花费了多少钱。所以我们可以猜测
that at 8 a.m. they woke up and then they had a cup of coffee before taking the
早上 8 点，他们起床，然后喝了一杯咖啡，然后才上床睡觉。
transport to their work so they probably have a 9 to 5 job and then we could also
上班的交通，所以他们可能有朝九晚五的工作，然后我们也可以
determine using assumption.
使用假设来确定。